RUPESH KUMAR SINGH

C/O RAJIV SINGH, FLAT NO. 7, PLOT NO. 12, VAISHNAVI PARK, DATTA NAGAR, CHUNCHLE, NASHIK, MH - 422010 8285069575 | rupeshks9575@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Multi-tasking Assistant Manager well-known for creating positive environments where employees can thrive and succeed. Detailed and fast-paced team player. Pursuing new sales-driven role where hard work and dedication will be highly valued. Excellent conflict resolution skills and more than 6 years of experience.

SKILLS

- Staff & Operations Management
- Computer literate
- Natural leader & Motivated team player
- Communication ability in English and Hindi

WORK HISTORY

VATSGRAM MARKETING

Assistant Manager | Khagaria Bihar | December 2017 – January 2019

- Team handling & responsible to addressing customer inquiries solving problems and providing new product information.
- Vendor management
- Data and MIS handling.

GREEN LENS VERIFICATION PVT LTD

Assistant Manager | New Delhi | April 2017 – November 2017

- Client handling Addressing problem with clients to promote quick and successful resolution.
- Handling Employee background verification department.

TACT INDIA PVT LTD

Senior Research Associate | Gurgaon, HR | March 2014 – February 2017

- Client handling Addressing problem with clients to promote quick and successful resolution.
- Handling Employee background verification Team.

EL CAMINO TECHNOLOGIES

Customer support Executive | Gurgaon, HR | April 2013 – February 2014

• Documentation all customer enquiries and comments thoroughly and quickly for website moderation.

DEFENCE SERVICES OFFICERS' INSTITUTE (DSOI)

Computer Operator | Gurgaon, HR | June 2012 – December 2012

• Resolving customer query and problems.

AEGIS BPO SERVICES (GURGAON) LIMITED

Customer support Executive | Gurgaon, HR | September 2009 – February 2011

• Resolving customer query and problems.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF ARTS (PSYCHOLOGY HONOURS.)

Lalit Narayan Mithila University | Darbhanga, Bihar | 2012

INTERMEDIATE (+2) Arts

Bihar Intermediate Education Council | Patna, Bihar | 2006

SECONDARY (10th)

Bihar School Examination Board | Patna, Bihar | 2003

COMPUTER DIPLOMA COURSE

Adarsh Technical Training Institute | New Delhi | 2010

Mobile Hardware & Software Training

Adarsh Technical Training Institute | New Delhi | 2010

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: 10th February 1988

Permanent address: Village: Durakpur, Post: Sahebpur Kamal

District: Begusarai, Bihar - 851217

Hobby: I like to practicing and teaching yoga.